circleid.com 2007-12-10

# CircleID - About CircleID

|  | 

#### Privacy Policy

CircleID believes in your right to privacy and is committed to the use of fair information practices on the Internet. This CircleID Privacy Statement applies to CircleID's website at www.CircleID.com (the "CircleID Site") and the services offered via the CircleID Site (the "CircleID Services"). By using the CircleID Site and/or the CircleID Services (collectively, "CircleID Site/Services"), you agree to the terms of this Privacy Statement.

**Types of Information Collected**

_Personal Information_. When you register to become a member of CircleID, you will be asked to provide certain personal information. Examples of the personal information that we collect include your name, email address, professional biography and occupation.

_IP Addresses_. An Internet protocol address ("IP address") is the unique number that identifies the computer you are using to browse the Internet. CircleID uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the CircleID Site, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Disclosure and Use of Information Collected**

Information Provided During Registration. The information you provide us when registering as a member of CircleID is publicly available on the CircleID Site as part of your member profile.

This means that your member profile may be viewed by other members and visitors of CircleID. You may choose to opt-out of this public disclosure of your member profile by [contacting us](http://www.circleid.com/about/contact/). You may change or edit information about yourself in your member profile at any time using your Member Panel.

_Posted Information_. The CircleID Site allows you to post information in public forums. Any information you voluntarily disclose through this medium is necessarily disclosed to the public.

_Email and Promotional Materials_. We send all new members a welcome email to verify password and username. In addition CircleID publishes a weekly email newsletter. This service is optional and may be administrated from the member control panel.

**Links**

The CircleID Site may contain images of and links to third party websites ("Linked Sites"). The Linked Sites are not under the control of CircleID and CircleID is not responsible for the content of any Linked Site. Use of information collected at Linked Sites is subject to any privacy policies at those sites.

**Data From Children**

CircleID does not collect data from individuals that identify themselves as children under the age of thirteen, and the CircleID Site/Services are not intended for use by children under the age of thirteen. If CircleID becomes aware that it has received information from a child under the age of thirteen, we will delete all personally identifiable information concerning that child from our records.

**Security**

CircleID wants your personal information to remain as secure as reasonably possible. CircleID secures the personal information you provide on computer servers in a controlled, secure environment, protected from unauthorized access. When highly confidential information, such as a credit card number, is transmitted over the Internet, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

**Changes to this Privacy Statement**

The CircleID Privacy Statement is subject to change at any time. If any material changes are made to this Privacy Statement, it will be posted here. By using the site after any such announcement, you agree to the terms of the amended Privacy Statement.

|   
---|---|---
